奴の性格上 すでに敵に 取り込まれたと言っていいな 俺を売りはしないだろうが
Chairman Netero gathered the top
leaders of the Hunter Association, the Zodiacs, for the purpose of
electing the next chairman.
うっかり口を滑らすことは 高確率で　あり得る
The Zodiacs... Twelve Hunters whose abilities
the chairman had recognized.
仕掛けるなら　２人の岐路
In emergencies, he entrusted
them with leading the Association.
俺が　倒す。
When nothing was happening, they
accompanied him in leisure activities.
ハァ　ハァ…。
Debate X Among X Zodiacs
Chairman!
ゴンとキルアを 狙っている　この男 名は　シュート＝マクマホン
I thought we had all the Zodiacs present, but the Rat is missing.
彼もまた モラウの弟子の一人である
The Vice Chairman is very busy, even at a time like this. It's because it is a time like this.
ダメだ…！
He's scrambling to secure votes for himself, I'm sure.
こんな状態じゃ 全然　歯が立たねえよ。
Chairman!
うん…　ナックルもまだ 実力の半分も出してないよ。
Ginta... You're loud, annoying, and you smell! Even the habitual slacker Ging showed up!
きっと。 そうだな。
Guess the Rat's just a scumbag.
でも　それでも　やるしかない。
What do you mean, "even" I showed up? I'll kill you, monkey.
ああ。
Go ahead and try it, dumbass.
周りに　人けは　なし
I can't accept this.
今が好機
Why didn't the chairman call us to help?
慎重に　そして　確実に ターゲットを仕留める
Agreed. Morel and Knov were above that kind of job!
それでこそ　ＵＭＡハンター
"Above" is not the word you're looking for.
ハァ　ハァ…。
You wanted to hunt the Ants yourself, did you not?
The chairman wanted all of us together for this. Let's wait for him to arrive.
行くぞ！　チャンスだ…
Everyone is in a frenzy over what's
going on with East Gorteau. It's a big problem.
何をしている… 絶好のチャンスだぞ
Just sit down.
今なら　確実に… う…！
Oh, sorry about that.
行け！
Then let's begin this meeting on the
election of the next chairman.
行け!!
Hold on! Why are you leading the meeting?
う…　うぅ…。
Don't boss us around after you showed up late. Pariston, you're irritating!
You're a creep! Get lost!
うっ　うっ…。
Well, I wasn't sure if I should take the lead.
シュート＝マクマホン
But you know, I'm the Vice Chairman.
彼は　気が弱かった
I outrank the rest of you, and I'm
good at coordinating these things. I'm sure you all want to finish this quickly.
ねぇ　キルア
If we rank by age, Botobai-san should lead.
何で　ナックルさんは ダメなんだろう？
Judging by ability to foster progress,
Cheadle-san should lead.
ん？　何が？ ＮＧＬへの参加！
Both are better suited to the task than I.
すごく強いと思うんだけどなぁ。
Would one of you be willing to take over?
まぁ　確かに。 基本的な体術は
I'll refrain. You'd probably give me a hard time.
精神面じゃねえの？
I concur.
精神面？
Forget it. Just lead the meeting.
奴のポリシーは　今回の目的には 全く沿わないし
Just come out and say you
want to do it, scumbag.
甘いよな…。 何か　動物にも 感情移入しそうだし。
In that case, if anyone objects
to me leading this meeting, raise your hand.
いつの間にか　進んで 俺達に協力してくれてるよね。
I object! I object! I seriously object!
周りにいる犬 さらに増えてたよな。 うん。
I see four objections... The majority says I should continue. Of course, we can discuss any
complaints as they arise.
「練」を維持できて来てるわね
Then, I have a proposal.
いい傾向だわさ これを３時間続けられれば 一度　万全な状態で 戦わせてみようかね
I will run for the position of chairman, so let's not bother with an election.
恐らく　それなら　ナックルも 全力で対応せざるを得なくなる
I'm gonna kill you, brat! Scary... Everyone calm down.
そこで　２人とも 気づけばいいけど
My point is that we'll waste time and money.
自分にないもの　必要なもの
We already know the results.
でも　気づけて　ようやく半分 順調に進んだとして
No one here will vote for you.
そこまで　たどり着くのに あと１０日前後
That's eleven votes.
つまり　その後の残り時間は 一日あるかないか
Together, you can only muster eleven votes.
間に合いそうもないわね
Do you know how many Hunters
are in the Association? The late Chairman Netero was too strong...
うぅ…　うぅ…。
So he couldn't understand
the feelings of the weak.
うぅ…　うぅ…！
The same can be said for all of you. However, I can understand the weak! That is the kind of Chairman I seek to be!
逃げる準備したほうが いいかもね　私だけでも
How much have you made off
them, Prince of Kickbacks? Please, you have it wrong. I'm asking
them to contribute to the pool.
召し上がれ。
It's meant to help the Association expand.
いただきます！ いただきます！
Eighteen people. Do you know what that number represents?
どうかしら…。
The number of Hunters who've
gone missing in the three years
うん！　すごくおいしいよ！
since you became Vice Chairman.
見たところ　ナックルに本気を 出させるための 基礎能力向上修行でさえ
As professionals who risk our lives, we're obligated to be aware of the
situations our trusted associates are in. A missing Hunter is more bizarre than
a Hunter's unexpected death.
３分の２程度しか 進んでないようだけど。
Before you became Vice Chairman, the
average was 0.6 Hunters missing per year.
アイタタタ… 正確に読まれてるわさ えっ!?　そうなの？　ビスケ。
It's increased tenfold.
でも　大丈夫！ 絶対勝つから！　期間内に！ ん…！
That number is tragic... It pains me greatly.
何で　そんなことが言えるの？ 状況は　一向に 良くなってないのに！
Once I become Chairman,
the number will surely decrease!
思ったこと　何でも 言っていいって言ったから 教えてあげましょうか？
I'm going to carry on the old man's will.
最近　私　気づくと包丁持って それをジッと見つめて 落ち着く自分がいるなって 思ってて
Don't want to vote for either of them!
これって ほぼ限界に近いってことだから。
Ging-san, I hear something
happened to your son...
手遅れになる前の 今なら逃げても
Sounds like it.
追っかけてまで殺そうとは 思わないと思うの。
Should I visit him?
これさえなけりゃ…
Sure, he'd probably be thrilled.
本当に　おいしい ごはんなんだけどね…
Would he even realize I was there? I heard he's in critical condition.
逃げないってば！ 何度も言ってるでしょ。
Maybe I shouldn't go after all...
逃げずに　どうするの？
If he dies after I do, I'll have wasted my time.
絶対　今のままじゃ 勝てっこないわよ。
Go visit him. He isn't going to die.
えっ？ ほら　早く！
Uh, can I ask a question?
あ…。 指切りげんまん　期間内に
First, shouldn't we reevaluate
the process for running?
ナックルとシュートを倒す
You're the one who started it!
ウソついたら 針千本　飲ます 指切った
What's wrong with your head?! I only offered to serve in hopes
of saving us money and time.
あ…　あ…。 俺の島では　その後　こうすんの！
If we can't avoid the process,
let's first decide how to go about it.
こうやって　親指をくっつけて…。 あ…！ 誓いの　チュ！ あ！
There we go! When he controls the pace, everything becomes more complicated.
はい！　約束完了。
In that case, we can draw lots.
ところで　パームさん このダシ　何？
Screw that! How can we have our leader chosen by chance?
ゴンの奴　どんどん パームのあしらい方
I'll give a sheet of paper to each of you. Hey...
うまくなってるよな。 そういう流れに 誘導している節が…。 クナイ産の地鶏を ひと晩　煮込んで
I want each of you to write what you believe to be the optimal election process, with the prerequisite of achieving
at least 95% voter turnout.
さらに　ひと晩　置いとくの。 あと１０日か…。
And a third party will pick one
of the proposals at random.
余命みたく言うなよ！
A third party? I'm guessing she means Beans.
これだ…
But we should write down our names,
so we know whose idea is chosen.
霧のように森を覆う煙
She said the odds are 1 in 12, but that isn't true.
テレパシー こちら　バイタル隊 ゴラン！　状況を知らせろ！
If the ten of us write something
that puts Pariston...
テレパシー ゴラン　応答しろ！
and Ging, if possible...
テレパシー ゴラン！ まさか…　もう消されたのか
at a disadvantage, our odds will be 5 in 6.
テレパシー ゴラン隊！　誰か！ 今の状況を説明しろ！ テレパシー いや　周りが煙だらけで 状況が把握できない
If we record how each person votes, Pariston will have an advantage.
テレパシー ゴラン隊長に呼びかけたが 返事がない
Should we use anonymous ballots to allow
for dividing points among candidates?
テレパシー さっきから 信号が途絶えたままだ テレパシー さっきまで横にいたんだ！
Would our intermediaries then
betray us with no guilt or fear?
チッ…。
So here we are, Beans-san.
信号が混じって 訳が分かんねえ
There are twelve sheets of paper inside.
師団長が 不在時の連絡網くらい
Please pick one.
きっちり決めとけよ！ テレパシー バイタル隊　前へ！
It will determine the rules
we will use for the election.
テレパシー ゴラン隊に合流　調査！
You want me to pick one?
テレパシー
This is an important task.
兵隊の信号数が　減って行く！
The chosen proposal is Ging-san's.
うわ！
Ging's rules...
He's no Pariston, but he's still trouble.
ふぅ　次は　おぬしらか…。
Rule #1. "All Hunters are both candidates and voters."
しかし　いいのかね。 何がだ？
"If the winner of the first election fails
to receive a majority of votes, the top sixteen will have a runoff.
俺達は　送るだけ 倒すのは　じいさん。
If a majority is still not achieved, there will
be another runoff with half the candidates."
ちょっと楽過ぎるな。
Rule #3.
しかし　確実だ。 まぁな。 謙遜していたが 会長は　まだまだ俺達より強いよ。
"If the turnout for any given vote is under
95%, that vote must be redone." Rule #4.
本人も　かなり乗り気だしな。 [TEL]
"Voters must write their name on the ballot.
Anonymous votes will be invalid."
おっ！　噂をすればだ。
What are you thinking?!
どんどん送っていいぞえ。
Are you an idiot? A total idiot?!
ようやく勘が戻って来たわい。
You are the idiots.
さすがですね。 フッ。
When everyone knows who voted for whom, it's a lot more entertaining.
で　女王のほうは？
There's his problem...
特に動きはありません。
He only cares about having fun!
女王は 巣に閉じこもったままです。
Rule #5. There's more?!
王は　まだ生まれてはおらん ということだな。
"The election committee chairman
will be Ging Freecss."
引き続き　監視を続けてくれ。
I didn't think of that!
了解です。
I didn't include such a rule...
じいさん　絶好調だ。 もう１隊　行っとくか？
That was a mistake. I was too focused on the actual rules.
ああ。
This is what Ging really wanted.
これで残るは　１４隊か…。
This drawing was to determine how the
election would be conducted, correct?
人間どもめ　一体どんな　てで 我々の部隊を次々と…。
Rules one through four are fine, but the chairman should be chosen separately. I can live with that.
分からん…　分かっているのは
You can?
人間にも　かなりのつわものがいる ということぐらいだ。
This is a Hunter.
そもそも俺達は 人間について知らな過ぎる。
Frightening...
我々以上の力を持っている。
Two Days Ago
もう少し時間があれば その力をも手に入れてやるのに。
Ging-san! Yo.
うむ　だが　王さえ生まれれば こっちのものだ。
What brings you here so early? I'm surprised you actually came.
ああ　そう願いたい。
Yeah, I happened to be in the area.
フフフ…。
I saw the old man's video.
ん？　早く出たいか？
Oh, that pen and notepad... Huh? Can you leave one by the phone
in the conference room?
ウフフ…　でもまだ。
Oh, there should already be one.
まだ出るのは早いわ…。
Oh, never mind, then.
はい！　３時間終了！ おっ　もう終わりか。
Why do you ask?
あれ？
Four...
ナックルと戦わないの？
No, eight.
体調を万全にしたら行くわよさ。
Read this.
倒しといで。 会長が言っていたリミットまでは あと一日ちょっと。
These are rules for the election, yes? Yeah.
これが最初で最後の チャンスかもよ。
What is this for? In a few days, the Zodiacs will gather here.
まっ　全力で戦った結果なら
Most likely, there will be a drawing.
どう転んでも 納得せざるを得ないわよね それぞれが 足りないものに気づけたら
Why would you say that? If we tried to hold a vote or come to a
consensus, it would take too long.
それだけで　十分収穫だわさ
Plus, Pariston will be there...
あっ！ うぅ…　ん…。 うぅ…　ん…。
As far as he's concerned, 1 in 12 odds would be acceptable,
as long as it might give him an advantage.
あっ…　あっ…。 うぅ…　うぅ…。
Either way, it's a win for him. And everyone else will think
their odds are 5 in 6...
問題は どうやって逃げるかね…
That basically guarantees a drawing. I expect Cheadle will propose it.
ん？
Everyone else in this building supports Pariston. If these rules look acceptable, fold it three
times, and keep it until the meeting.
今夜は　マジみてぇだな。
In my opinion, if you're willing
to become Chairman...
おはよう　ユピー。
committee members are present,
and identification has been verified.
ユピー？
The voting takes place in the Hunter
Association headquarters.
正確に言うと モントゥトゥユピーですけどね。
As long as three or more
committee members are present, absentee ballots may be entered
at a different location.
腹へった。
The vote will take place
戦う前に　もう一人の居場所を 聞きたいんだけど。 あぁ？　シュートのことか。
from 12:00 AM on August 8th
to 11:59:59 PM on August 8th. This will not change. Any voting that occurs away from headquarters
must follow this schedule.
うん。 聞いてどうする気だ！　おい。
Votes will be tallied the same day.
これから ぶちのめされちまうのによ。 割符は２枚必要だからね。
And it is now August 8th, 12:00 AM.
笑わすじゃねえか。
The vote begins.
くっ！
a murderer would be interested
in such an ordinary event.
オラ！
Eighty-five points.
うっ…！ ゴン！
Yes, I'm not interested. See? It's blank.
重い！ 体の内側まで痺れる感じだ
Then why are you here?
「堅」を解いたら
Ninety points...
どこを殴られても 即　ＫＯされる！
Is someone named Ging here?
肩慣らしに４５発撃ったら 本気でやるぜ。
I'd like to speak to him. He's already gone...
気ぃつけたほうがいいぞ！　こら。
He said the next time we see
him here will be at the runoff.
俺は　尻上がりだからな。
Why don't you take your paper and leave?
[TEL]　今日も出て来んのか。
Seventy-seven points.
ええ。
Okay.
[TEL]　巣に貯蔵されている 人体の数から推測すると
You're bothering us!
一週間くらいで 補給が必要になるはずです。
Get lost! Aren't you done here?
その時に　あと２３隊 消しておきたいところですしね。 うん　任せる。
He's assessing the goods.
動くのは　弟子の結果を 待ってからだそうだ。
Ten points, two points, fifty points, thirty points.
ふん　無駄だと思うがね。 ナックル達ならまだしも
I guess pro Hunters are still nothing special...
じいさんのほうの弟子は 不安要素が多過ぎる。 戦力として　計算できないんじゃ
If I want someone to fight,
it'll have to be a Zodiac.
せいぜい　おとりぐらいしか 使い道ねえだろ。
Ninety-five points!
俺達も賭けるか？ 明日どっちの弟子が来るか？
Ah, I have the results for the
13th chairman's election.
俺はナックルとシュートに １０万ジェニー。
Election for the 13th Chairman
1) Pariston — 249 (37.6%)
2) Cheadle — 42
3) Ickshonpe — 26
4) Botobai, Mizaistom — 17
6) Saccho — 14
7) Ginta — 13
8) Morel — 12
9) Piyon, Cluck — 11
11) Cutie, Sanbica — 10
13) Teradein — 9
もしも　お互いハズれたら 会長にプレゼント。
Valid votes, 580. Invalid votes, 48.
乗るか？
14) Bushidora — 8
15) Ging — 7
6) Linne, Tsezguerra, Biscuit — 6
19) Knov, Loupe — 5
21) Kite, Geru, Kanzai, 2 others — 4
26) Satotz, Menchi, 7 others — 3
35) Hisoka, Saiyu, 9 others — 2
46) Gon, Hanzo, 25 others — 1 Absentees, 33.
そうだな　じゃあ　僕は…。
(Wrote own name only, misspelled name,
voted for previous chairman, no name given, etc.)
(Gon, Shoot, Kurapika, Killua,
Shalnark, and others, totaling 28) None of the candidates received a majority. The turnout was 87.7%.
…に１００万。 はぁ？ あるわけねえだろ！　そんなこと。
As the conditions were not met,
the vote must be redone.
わざわざ　金　ドブに捨てる気か？
Hey! Can't I take a look? No.
会長はドブですか？
I'm just curious!
はぁ… 僕もギャンブル好きでしてね。
I won't allow anyone to view the ballots.
もっぱら　大穴狙いなんです。
Since I was designated election chairman, this is my decision to make.
くっ！
It's no fun if I can't see who voted for whom! Scrooge! Baldy!
オラ！
Moron.
はっ！
Are you bored?
ガハっ！
And yourself?
くっ！
So, Hisoka...
これで　肩慣らし… クッソ…　強い！
Rumors say he died alongside
the mutant Ants he was fighting, and the Association received
a lot of land in reward.
それにしても ナックルは…　まさか…
Ants? As I thought.
おい　使わねえのかよ　あれ。 最初は　グってやつ。
A lot's happened around the world, while you were chasing Chrollo.
まっ　使えねえだろうな。 欠陥品だもんな　ありゃよ。
If you'd stopped to think for a moment, you could have fought the
chairman or the Ants.
欠陥品だと？
That would require stopping to think...
言っとくがな おめぇがあれを使おうとしても
Maybe you can become my manager?
速攻　潰すぜ！
Gon and Killua also joined the Ant hunt.
タイマンで　あの技を 使えると思うなよ　こら。
Gon's on the verge of death, and Killua's
gone to speak to our father.
てめぇのあの技には
At this rate, they'll both die.
２つ　デッケェ弱点がある！
Both of them? I can't have that happen.
この任務　果たせぬかもな…
I want to get rid of him.